Slow down.
Don't fall.
You're a big boy now,
but you still act like a little kid.
Granny, I'm already grown up.
Okay.
Granny.
Look at the moon in the sky. It's so round!
It really is.
The moon is round,
and we're reunited too.
Granny,
when I grow up,
Lots of brown sugar glutinous rice cakes!
Okay.
My Xiwa is such a good boy.
Granny will be waiting.
In your case,
I'm afraid we'll need to
proceed with a needle biopsy.
Doctor,
whatever it is,
just give it to me straight.
From the scans, it looks like cancer.
But we still have to wait
for the pathology results to be sure.
What?
Cancer?
I understand.
Coming through! Make way!
Granny Xiufang, we're almost there.
Just hold on a little longer.
Careful.
Today,
I thought I'd give you a little report.
I've been forced to retire.
But you don't need to worry.
Dealing with the dead,
to me,
is just an everyday routine.
If the King of Hell approves the paperwork,
I'll go run the errands.
In a flash, I've done this for decades.
I've sent off so many people.
This time,
it's my turn.
Yueru, you have no idea.
This disease requires chemotherapy.
When that time comes,
my hair will all fall out.
I'll be bedridden,
with tubes hooked up all over my body.
Not only will I suffer half to death,
but I'll also burden the family.
It's not that I'm afraid.
I just
didn't get enough time with my kids.
Just thinking that
I'll be seeing you so soon...
It...
it makes me feel a little better.
All my life,
I haven't left the kids anything.
Let me leave them something to remember.
You're still laughing?
Okay, okay, okay.
You're right.
Smile.
Smiling is better than crying.
I'll remember that.
Smiling... is better than crying.
Assembly at the altar,
chant the holy name.
Bitter sea surges, calling the lost souls,
yet the deluded refuse to awaken.
If mortals fail to chant Amitabha,
they walk this world in vain.
You already know.
Know what?
Then why are you looking at me like that?
Dad.
I have a favor to ask.
I get it.
If you really don't want to do this,
then don't.
If you want to leave, just go.
I want to learn Hospice care.
I wanted to teach you before,
but you couldn't care less.
Is the sun rising in the west today?
It's just that I have...
people and things I want to care for now.
You heartless brat.
But you never care about your old man.
Do I not care about you?
I tell you to cut back, but do you listen?
You knucklehead!
Boss Chen, I'm driving!
You've done funerals for a while now.
You should know that Death knows no age.
Quick, take that back!
I'd make you knock on wood if we had any.
How can we mind talking about death?
I mind when it's the people I care about.
Based on the patient's current condition,
although she isn't terminal yet,
but some of her organs have shut down.
It's normal for her not to eat or drink.
So at a time like this,
we can't force food or drinks on her.
Right now, we just need a cotton swab
dipped in a little water
to help moisten the patient's lips.
We can also
ask the doctor to give her some glucose
and saline or something.
Got it?
That's unnecessary.
The patient is dehydrated right now,
and her blood flows very slowly.
We can't cover her with anything heavy.
The patient is extremely fragile now.
Even the slightest bit of weight
will make her feel incredibly exhausted.
Everything I just told you,
you need to learn it by heart.
I got it.
Who'll remind you when I'm gone?
Quick, knock on wood!
Pour some warm water.
Dementia can cause a lot of complications.
At this stage,
their organs are failing,
and their whole body is in agony.
So we need to
gently rotate her arms for her.
Remember, follow the meridians.
The arms.
We can also help wipe her forehead,
and lightly pat her back.
Our job
is to make the patients' final journey
more comfortable.
Just give it a try.
Grandma.
The jasmine you grew
has bloomed.
I brought you the most fragrant pot.
This way,
you can smell it
and feel like
you're home.
Soul
Social
What are you looking at?
Why so nervous?
I do funeral services,
and you do wedding planning.
It's not like I'm gonna steal your ideas.
I'm just afraid a Top-tier grad like you
will look down on a middle school grad.
You're making fast progress.
You even make presentations on a PC now.
To be honest,
if I train my brain a bit,
I think there's still hope for me.
The problem is this brain is failing me.
I thought about it over and over,
and I feel my head just can't keep up.
What was that thing you told me about?
What is it?
Business model.
Right, right.
That business model.
I think our Xi Dong Dong is really
a complete mess.
You know?
There's so much to do.
If I don't sort it out,
I won't have a job anymore.
I'll be an industry jinx again.
Aren't Zhou Fang and Xu Wumei there?
Those two idiots?
No ideas, no plans, no creativity.
They do things randomly,
like blindly groping in the ocean.
Just groping blindly.
Not bad, Wu Huilan.
You even have strategic thinking now.
What?
Strategic thinking?
What the heck is strategic thinking?
Simply put, strategic thinking
is
setting a long-term goal first.
Then you stand tall and look far.
How tall? And how far?
Explain it to me specifically.
Based on user needs,
you take the high ground
and begin with the end in mind.
It's so competitive now,
we must provide high-standard service
to attract high-quality users.
Using all these idioms...
I'm really a bit confused.
Tell me in detail.
What exactly are user needs?
User needs mean
different people want different things.
You provide exactly what they want.
You categorize them.
What does "take the high ground" mean?
High ground, high ground.
You choose a high place,
and look down from above.
Have a big picture view.
So "begin with the end in mind"...
does that mean
I should think about the outcome first,
and then work backwards
to see what to do at the very beginning?
Right.
That's exactly what it means.
Your...
your brain is actually pretty sharp.
Duh.
Your mom might not be highly educated,
but I'm not dumb.
If I were dumb,
how could I have such a smart daughter?
Alright, alright.
The faintest ink is better than the best memory.
Write it down.
Okay.
What thinking?
Strategic thinking.
Do you know how to write it?
"Stra-"
Is this how you spell "stra"?
Right.
"-tegic."
"-tegic." T-E...
G-I-C?
Right.
Yes, G-I-C.
"Think-"
"-ing."
Great.
Beautiful, truly beautiful.
Shiqi's playing
has improved again.
You flatter her, Director Wang.
This child
started learning to play at three.
As for having exquisite skills,
she still has a long way to go.
You're being too modest.
Not only is Shiqi beautiful,
she excels in Music, chess, calligraphy, and painting.
This is all thanks to you, her mother,
for your careful cultivation.
Lao Fan,
you raised a star of a daughter.
Not at all.
Director Wang,
about what happened last time,
I still need to apologize to you.
It's good that young people have character.
Come, let me refill your glass.
Uncle Fan,
about what happened last time,
I was also at fault.
Shiqi told me
it was a misunderstanding.
Easygoing girls like her are rare now.
Listen to him.
Our Xiao Wang is so sensible.
Come on,
let me propose another toast to everyone.
Great, come on.
Cheers.
Drink up, drink up.
All right.
Cheers.
Come, Shiqi.
Let's have a drink.
It was all a misunderstanding before.
Shiqi.
Shiqi
I've really spoiled her.
It's fine, it's fine.
Come on, Director Wang.
Come, come, come.
Come on, let's drink.
Let's keep drinking.
Uncle Fan.
Director Wang.
About what we agreed on tonight...
...when you sober up tomorrow morning...
...you can't go back on your word.
A gentleman's word is his bond.
Good, good, good.
Good.
I sincerely hope...
...that we...
...can unite our families.
No need to see me out.
Okay.
Take care, Director Wang.
See you another day.
Goodbye.
Take care, take care.
Lao Fan.
Look at you.
During dinner just now...
...what was with that look on your face?
Dad.
Is my marriage...
...just a bargaining chip for your business?
I'm your father.
Do you think I'd ever hurt you?
Everything I'm doing now...
...is all for your own good.
Since I was little...
...my mom decided what I wore.
What school I went to...
...what major I chose...
...what kind of life I lived...
...and what job I got...
...you arranged absolutely everything.
But when it comes to marriage...
...this time...
...can you please let me choose for myself?
Living in this world...
...is all about equivalent exchange.
What you want isn't important.
What matters is what you can offer them.
But I'm your daughter.
I'm not some commodity for you to trade.
You're determined to marry that Vulture...
...and let him take over my company?
Don't think I can't see what you're up to.
Throwing yourself at him...
...have you no shame?
You had someone watch me?
What else? Was I supposed to just watch you...
...be with that punk?
He might not even be interested in you.
Enough!
And about this contract...
When you get engaged to Xiao Wang...
...only then will I sign this contract.
Whether you agree to this contract...
...what does it have to do with them?
I am a businessman.
You should understand this principle.
You're getting completely out of line.
Granny.
You're awake.
Xiwa.
Granny.
You can't take that off.
I brought you some food.
Granny's awake.
Granny.
I'll go get the doctor.
Granny, you can't touch that.
Granny, how are you feeling now?
You've been asleep for days.
Who... are you?
It's me, Xizi.
The Xizi who loves brown sugar glutinous rice cakes.
Xiwa
Late-stage Alzheimer's disease is agony.
Aside from memory loss,
physical decline is the most fatal part.
Regardless,
it slowly drains all memory and vitality.
Then... is there any chance she can recover?
Talk to her more about the past.
Don't put too much pressure on her.
Eventually, getting dressed, eating,
washing up, and using the toilet need help.
Her mood will fluctuate.
You need to show more care and patience.
At this stage,
returning to a familiar environment
would be better for her.
Okay.
Let's go.
Thank you, doctor.
Hello?
Ma'am?
Who are you looking for?
Ma'am.
Say something.
You...
Ma'am.
Don't scare me.
Ma'am
Why can't I remember?
Xiwa.
Pour Grandma some water.
All washed.
Dry off.
Okay.
I poured it.
Xiwa
Grandma
What's wrong, Grandma?
In here
is the money I saved,
and
your dad
and mom's
accident
Compensation.
Now that you're back,
while I still remember,
I'm giving all this
to you early.
Grandma, keep it for now.
You'll live a long life.
I know my own body.
I've just been holding on,
just waiting for you to come back.
Now that you're back,
keep it safe.
Grandma...
You're my grandchild,
it should go to you.
If you don't take it, who will?
Keep it safe.
The ancients believed wood
represents immortality,
so making a coffin out of wood
reflects their wish for eternal life.
Have you ever heard the saying,
"Seeing is believing"?
But seeing pales to firsthand experience.
You want to test the coffin?
When in Shanghai, people I knew tried it.
It made me really want to try it myself.
And now here's my chance.
Take off your shoes.
How does it feel?
It's amazing.
I felt so peaceful the moment I lay in it.
Lying in this big wooden box,
looking at the world from this angle,
it feels completely different.
Of course it does.
It feels like, aside from life and death,
everything else is just a scratch.
Wanna try it?
Speaking of firsthand experience,
I've actually played many corpses before.
Cut!
Great job, guys!
We got it.
We got it! The director said we got it!
You guys did great.
Stop playing dead.
We got it! We got it!
Not bad.
I heard the director talking about you.
He said your performance... as this corpse...
was incredibly lifelike.
Really?
Even I bought it. Damn right.
Seriously.
Thank you, Director!
A lifelike corpse?
Is he complimenting you or insulting you?
No matter how well you play a corpse,
you're still nothing but a lousy extra.
Give it a try.
It definitely feels different.
Okay.
How does it feel?
Lying in the real deal feels different.
Daxi, I really can't take this anymore.
You don't look so good today.
Don't go to your part-time job.
Go home and get some rest.
I can't do that.
But for today,
you play the toad.
I'll play the clown.
Why?
The last time you used that greasepaint,
you had a severe allergic reaction to it.
Chen Baixi!
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
Slow down, slow down.
Let me catch my breath.
No...
My shoes!
Chen Baixi!
What's going on?
You were lying there perfectly fine.
Are you possessed or something?
You didn't even grab your shoes!
It's fine.
If you don't want to talk about it, don't.
Actually...
I didn't return because I was blacklisted.
I knew it!
What rich lady has that much power?
It was because my best friend passed away.
He was my college classmate.
After we graduated,
we worked part-time and acted.
We lived together in a tiny rented room,
ate instant noodles,
and dreamed of becoming actors.
The day he died,
he was just cast for a role the next day.
He was so excited.
He finally got to show his talent.
Since his graduation,
that was his happiest day.
But I never expected...
that night,
he wouldn't make it to dawn.
The doctor said it was sudden death.
There was no time to save him.
But I still can't help but wonder,
if that day...
if I hadn't let him go to work that night,
or if I had done something more,
would he not have died?
Chen Baixi,
it wasn't your fault.
We always think that
if we had done a little more back then,
a little less,
or not done something at all,
could we have changed the future?
Could we make everything around us better?
But it doesn't work that way.
Some things are simply unpredictable.
birth, aging, sickness, and death...
Joy, sorrow, meeting, and parting...
Life is always full of regrets.
I know all that.
But I still think of how excited he was.
So I ran away.
Only by putting on a mask
can I hide myself away.
I really don't understand.
Since God gave him hope,
why did He have to take him away?
Well, look at it from another angle.
He was happy when he passed.
Because he left with hope,
instead of regret.
We always say tomorrow will be better,
but often, we just die tonight.
Why?
Hello, Director Ma.
Baixi,
the old lady is fading fast!
She's holding on to her last breath!
Hurry to the hospital!
Granny Xiufang!
Wait for me!
Xiwa!
Quick, over here!
Granny.
Granny, it's Xizi.
My child...
Granny has something
to tell you.
Tell me, Granny.
My child...
Don't look back.
Granny!
My child...
For twenty years...
at home,
I've been eating all alone.
Grandma made this chicken soup
for you.
Is it good?
Then,
Grandma will make more for you tomorrow.